[{"answer": "Charlize Theron.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "How do you actually pronounce your name?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "Charlize Theron.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "What is the correct South African, dare I say it, African way of pronouncing this?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "And you quite consciously went and taught yourself how to speak in an American accent, right?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Every day.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Do you speak African certainly?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Can you speak African to her?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Oh, I think more fluently than I speak English.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "So you speak it completely fluently?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Woody?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "None of this -- there's no truth to it whatsoever.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Guilty as charged?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "But he calls you Chuck?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Because I want to actually work until I'm 108, and I don't think you can't have longevity if you just kind of fall back on one aspect of what you are.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Heading that way?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think human beings are -- I think we're pretty complicated.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "There's never the safe one, is there?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Yes, we got plenty of time, seriously.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Oh, dear God, what is this an hour show?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "So far, I said.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Do you really love the aging process?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Look, I'm only 35.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Is that because it's obviously treating you quite well?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "I -- the first thing I do is I inspect every closet and drawer.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "So you get to these random houses, and what do you do?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "There are guys going to say who is this weirdo?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "I've gotten a lot better.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "It's fascinating watching you because I know you don't like watching yourself, do you?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "God, no.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Do you know how much money you've taken at the box office in movies you've been in?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "That sounds good.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "That's not bad, is it?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "I care.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "You don't care how much they make, these films?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "I guess I would take the one that makes the billion dollars, but the critics don't care for it because then I can go make seven of the ones that I love.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Which one would you prefer at this stage of your career?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "I'm sorry.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Hey, Todd, do we even have factory work?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "That was the greatest gift I think I've ever been given in my career.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "I mean, when you look back on it now, obviously brilliant for you in your career, but to actually play that role, what was the experience like?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Yes, look, it's absolutely amazing to win an Academy Award.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "I did, yes.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Did you watch the Oscars as a young girl?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Have you met him?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "The first time I met him, I had just won the Academy Award.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "When did you meet him?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "The nicest things that any icon or hero could possibly say to you.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "And what did he say to you?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Just, you know, giving me credit for being a South African and kind of putting South Africa on the map, which I didn't, but I'll take that any day from Nelson Mandela.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Any other?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Women?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "I don't know if they were women but I know another category South Africans have won.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Who else?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Look, I don't know.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "How much of it is down to what happened, if anything?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "No, it doesn't haunt me.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Does it haunt you?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "He was a -- he was a fun guy.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "But, there must be things that you got from your father?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "HERON: I think it's a lack of education.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "And what can be done to tackle it properly do you think?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "You can go to our web site, CharlizeAfricaOutreach.org.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "How can you get them?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "And -- yes, directly -- look, here's the thing.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "And directly help?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "It's been -- it's knowledge.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Is that the problem?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "I'll explain why.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "There are a few.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "What issues in America wind you up?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Yes, I think he's incredibly capable of it.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Do you still feel with Obama that he is capable of being as great as everybody hoped?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I -- I don't.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Do you think you'll never get married?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "You know this was never about the gold.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "What do you want?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "That is so -- no -- a few.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "No, a few.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "How many fingers?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "You know, I really love my job and I love my fans, but when it comes to my relationships, it's something that I keep very sacred to me, it's very private.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Why was that, do you think?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "No, and after --", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Am I allowed to pry?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "-- if they had images of you spoon-feeding this --", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "If you ate that taco?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, it was just such an innocent introduction.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "This is the problem when you're single and your friends kind of come out to help you and, you know, take you out for a nice meal and --", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Any -- any truth to that?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "No, I've known Keanu for over 15 years.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Not a sliver of truth?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "I'm not trying to pull you.", "docId": "111223pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Aren't you married?", "qSentId": 662}]